So First some basic vocabulary things that we'll need to know for this.
因此，首先我们需要了解一些基本词汇。
Lesson number one.
第一课。
Chores chores are the things we usually do around the house could be in the House could be outside of
家务 家务是我们通常在房子周围做的事情 可能在房子里 可能在外面
the house.
房子。
This might include mowing the lawn.
这可能包括修剪草坪。
It might include dusting.
它可能包括除尘。
It might include taking out the garbage we say garbage in America instead of rubbish which is what people
它可能包括取出我们在美国所说的垃圾而不是垃圾，这就是人们所说的
in the UK will say and many other parts of the world.
在英国会说和世界许多其他地方。
So these kinds of things around the house we call chores.
所以这些房子周围的事情我们称之为家务。
When I was a little boy every Sunday I had to dust the house that was my job.
当我还是个小男孩的时候，每个星期天我都不得不为我的工作打扫房子。
I had to dust the house I had to go around with a rag and some special cleaner and clean all the surfaces
我不得不打扫房子我不得不用抹布和一些特殊的清洁剂四处走动并清洁所有表面
in the House to make sure everything looked shiny and nice and new.
在房子里，以确保一切看起来都闪亮、漂亮和新。
That was my Sunday chore and I had other chores as well like feeding my cat and taking out the cat litter
那是我周日的家务，我还有其他家务，比如喂我的猫和取出猫砂
sometimes taking out the garbage.
有时倒垃圾。
This kind of thing.
这种事。
Its chores errands then are a little different.
它的家务事有点不同。
What's an Aaron.
什么是亚伦。
Well Aaron is a little bit more difficult to explain but it's kind of similar to chores.
好吧，亚伦有点难以解释，但它有点类似于家务。
It's something we have to do.
这是我们必须做的事情。
Usually it's not something we do for fun.
通常这不是我们为了好玩而做的事情。
We don't dust the house for fun.
我们打扫房子不是为了好玩。
We go out to do it.
我们出去做。
That means we don't stay home.
这意味着我们不会呆在家里。
It's kind of like a chore but outside and we're usually doing it pretty quickly pretty quickly.
这有点像一件苦差事，但在外面，我们通常很快就完成了。
It's not something that takes two or three hours.
这不是需要两三个小时的事情。
The best way to really get a feel for this would be some very quick examples and what errands are not
真正了解这一点的最好方法是一些非常简单的例子，而差事不是
OK.
好的。
Well going to the dentist is something we have to do.
去看牙医是我们必须做的事情。
But that might take an hour or two hours.
但这可能需要一两个小时。
Is that a an errand.
这是一个差事。
No.
不。
Usually going to the dentist is not an errand not an errand.
通常去看牙医不是差事，不是差事。
What about going shopping you might need to buy something I don't know what I need to buy but I need
去购物怎么样，你可能需要买一些我不知道我需要买但我需要的东西
to buy something maybe a jacket I go to a shop and look around.
买一些东西，也许是一件夹克，我去一家商店四处看看。
No.
不。
Usually when we run an errand and we often put run in front of an errand we could also say do an errand.
通常当我们跑腿时，我们经常把跑腿放在跑腿的前面，我们也可以说做跑腿。
We have it in our mind what we're going to do before we leave home.
在我们离开家之前，我们已经想到了我们要做什么。
So it's in mind I'm going to go to the supermarket to buy some tomatoes.
所以我打算去超市买些西红柿。
So we go out we go to the supermarket we buy some tomatoes and we come back.
所以我们出去了，我们去超市买了一些西红柿，然后我们回来了。
If we just say oh I might go hang out at the shopping center and maybe I'll buy some thing I need.
如果我们只是说哦，我可能会去购物中心闲逛，也许我会买一些我需要的东西。
Probably not an errand.
应该不是差事。
What about staying at home and paying your phone bill something you need to do.
待在家里并支付您需要做的事情的电话费怎么样。
Well no because that is not going out.
好吧，不，因为那不会出去。
You have to go out to run an errand.
你必须出去办事。
OK how about having a quick lunch with maybe a colleague.
好吧，和同事一起吃个快餐怎么样。
I have to meet them.
我必须见他们。
Have to have a quick lunch.
必须吃个快餐。
Only 30 minutes.
只有30分钟。
No because it's it's a social thing.
不，因为它是一种社会现象。
It's still a social thing and social things are not usually considered errands so things like maybe
这仍然是一件社交的事情，社交的事情通常不被认为是差事，所以像也许这样的事情
dropping off books get something repaired buy maybe food like groceries and maybe make an appointment
还书 修理东西 买些食物，比如杂货
at the at the dentist's office.
在牙医的办公室。
Make an appointment go to the dentist and you say I'd like to make an appointment.
预约 去看牙医，你说我想预约。
That kind of thing can be considered an errand.
这样的事情可以算作差事。
OK we'll talk about that more later in the class.
好的，我们稍后会在课堂上讨论这个。
Housework is often the same as chores housework is only in the home usually chores can be a little bit
家务往往和家务一样 家务只是在家里通常做家务可能会有点
more general strewn is when things are all over the place and we often use strewn when we're talking
更一般的散布是当事情到处都是，我们经常在谈话时使用散布
about clothes we have clothes strewn around the house they're all over the house they're all messed
关于衣服 我们的房子到处都是衣服 他们到处都是 他们都乱七八糟
up and we need to probably clean them up so we use strewn to describe this sort of messy or chaotic
起来，我们可能需要清理它们，所以我们用散落来描述这种凌乱或混乱
chaotic feeling detergent.
混乱的感觉洗涤剂。
Now we're gonna talk a little about laundry detergent is the main soap that we use for usually laundry
现在我们要谈谈洗衣粉是我们通常用于洗衣的主要肥皂
for this one which is washing clothes when you wash clothes you say you're doing laundry What are you
对于这个正在洗衣服的人，当你洗衣服时，你说你在洗衣服，你是什么
doing laundry.
洗衣服。
I need to do laundry today.
我今天需要洗衣服。
We don't usually say I need to wash my clothes.
我们通常不会说我需要洗衣服。
We usually say I need to do laundry.
我们通常说我需要洗衣服。
It's a chore.
这是一件苦差事。
It's a kind of housework.
这是一种家务。
Is it an errand.
是不是差事。
No.
不。
Buying detergent at the supermarket would be an errand because you say to yourself I need detergent.
在超市买洗衣粉会很麻烦，因为你对自己说我需要洗衣粉。
Go out you buy it come back.
出去买回来。
That's an error in doing the laundry at home.
这是在家洗衣服的错误。
That is a chore that is housework.
那是家务活。
And then softener is something that you put in to the washing machine with the detergent to make the
然后柔软剂是你和洗涤剂一起放入洗衣机中的东西
clothes softer.
衣服更柔软。
So they usually go together.
所以他们经常一起去。
They work together.
他们一起工作。
When you do laundry you use detergent and fabric softener.
当你洗衣服时，你会使用洗涤剂和织物柔软剂。
So these are just some keywords.
所以这些只是一些关键词。
I want you to keep in mind.
我要你记住。
And again we'll go through some specific examples later on in the lesson.
我们将在本课的稍后部分再次介绍一些具体示例。